var questions = [
    {
      question:
        "Q 1 -Which of the following is correct about features of JavaScript?",
      answers: [
        "A - JavaScript is is complementary to and integrated with HTML",
        "B - JavaScript is open and cross-platform.",
        "C - Both of the above",
        "D - All of the above",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "B - JavaScript is open and cross-platform.",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Q 2 - Which of the following type of variable is visible only within a function where it is defined?",
      answers: [
        "A - global variable",
        "B - local variable",
        "C - Both of the above.",
        "D - None of the above",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "B - local variable",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Q 3 - Which of the following function of Number object formats a number with a specific number of digits to the right of the decimal?",
      answers: [
        "A - toExponential()",
        "B - toFixed()",
        "C - toPrecision()",
        "D - toLocaleString()",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "B - toFixed()",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Q 4 - Which of the following function of String object returns a number indicating the Unicode value of the character at the given index?",
      answers: [
        "A - charAt()",
        "B - charCodeAt()",
        "C - concat()",
        "D - indexOf()",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "B - charCodeAt()",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Q 5 - Which of the following function of String object returns a number indicating whether a reference string comes before or after or is the same as the given string in sort order?",
      answers: [
        "A - localeCompare()",
        "B - search()",
        "C - substr()",
        "D - concat()",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "A - localeCompare()",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Q 6 - Which of the following function of String object returns the calling string value converted to lower case?",
      answers: [
        "A - toLocaleLowerCase()",
        "B - toLowerCase()",
        "C - toString()",
        "D - substring()",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "B - toLowerCase()",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Q 7 - Which of the following function of String object causes a string to be italic, as if it were in an <i> tag?",
      answers: [
        "A - fixed()",
        "B - fontcolor()",
        "C - fontsize()",
        "D - italics()",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "D - italics()",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Q 8 - Which of the following function of Array object removes the last element from an array and returns that element?",
      answers: ["A - pop()", "B - push()", "C - join()", "D - map()"],
      correctAnswer: "A - pop()",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Q 9 - Which of the following function of Array object represents the source code of an object?",
      answers: [
        "A - toSource()",
        "B - splice()",
        "C - toString()",
        "D - unshift()",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "A - toSource()",
    },
    {
      question: "Q 10 - Can you assign a anonymous function to a variable?",
      answers: [
        "A - true",
        "B - false",
        "C - only if it is one line long.",
        "D - all functions are anonymous",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "A - true",
    },
  ];